pyperf-before
=============

WARNING: the benchmark result may be unstable
* the standard deviation (181 ms) is 15% of the mean (1.25 sec)

Try to rerun the benchmark with more runs, values and/or loops.
Run 'python.exe -m pyperf system tune' command to reduce the system jitter.
Use pyperf stats, pyperf dump and pyperf hist to analyze results.
Use --quiet option to hide these warnings.

pyperf-after
============

WARNING: the benchmark result may be unstable
* the standard deviation (122 ms) is 13% of the mean (927 ms)

Try to rerun the benchmark with more runs, values and/or loops.
Run 'python.exe -m pyperf system tune' command to reduce the system jitter.
Use pyperf stats, pyperf dump and pyperf hist to analyze results.
Use --quiet option to hide these warnings.
